Exercise 7-5, Reading Reduced Sounds. Repeat the paragraph after me. Although
you're getting rid of the vowel sounds, you want to maintain a strong intonation
and let the sounds flow together. For the first reading of this paragraph, it's
helpful to keep your teeth clenched together to reduce excess jaw and lip
movement. Let's begin. Hello, my name is Anne. I'm taking American accent training.
There's a lot to learn, but I hope to make it as enjoyable as possible. I should pick
up on the American intonation pattern pretty easily, although the only way to
get it is to practice all the time. I use the up and down or peaks and valleys
intonation more than I used to. I've been paying attention to pitch, too. It's like
walking down a staircase. I've been talking to a lot of Americans lately, and
they tell me that I'm easier to understand.
Anyway, I could go on and on, but the important thing is to listen well and
sound good. Well, what do you think? Do I?